(sighs)
Here we go again.
(Penny:)Why is everyone so concerned
with us setting a date?
(Penny:)We're committed to
each other. We're happy.
(Penny:)A ceremony isn't gonna
change anything.
(Sheldon:)So you're never getting married?
(Sheldon:)It's his whining, isn't it?
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I'm not a whiner.
(Sheldon:)It's amusing
that he doesn't hear it.
(Leonard:)Look, all she's saying
is we are in love
(Leonard:)so it doesn't matter
if we get married
(Leonard:)tomorrow or a year from now
or 50 years from now.
(Penny:)Ew, 50?
We'll be old and gross.
(Leonard:)Yeah, but we'll be old
and gross together.
SHELDON:
My aunt and uncle
(Sheldon:)were married 63 years.
(Sheldon:)Towards the end, it was
like watching cheese melt.
(Penny:)Um... I'm
free tonight.